Guide to the Ephemera collection, 1835-2002 MS2380
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Ephemera, 1835-2002; Series 2
  - Memorial service of James Abram Garfield, President March 4th 1881, died September 19th 1881. Age 49 years. Eulogy of Hon. James C. Blaine, House of Representatives Feby. 27th 1882. John Sherman, Chairman Senate Committee. Wm. McKinley, Jr., Chairman House Committee., Series 2; 1 card. 15 x 25 cm (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 4
    Cataloger notes: With admission pass to the Rotunda.
    Subjects: Garfield, James A. (James Abram), 1831-1881. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n50015182; Garfield, James A. (James Abram), 1831-1881 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00004703
  - Inaugural ceremonies of Grover Cleveland, president, and Adlai E. Stevenson, vice-president. March 4, 1893. Final report of the General Committee and of the Executive Committee ..., Circa [1893]; Series 2; 48 pages group of portraits, facsimile 24 cm (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 5
    Cataloger notes: Text on inner side of covers.
    Subjects: Cleveland, Grover, 1837-1908 Inauguration, 1893.; Cleveland, Grover, 1837-1908 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00009698; 1893 fast; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743
  - Cleveland and Stevenson inaugural ceremonies, March 4, 1893: officers and members of the General, Executive, and sub-committees., Circa [1892?]; Series 2; 60 pages; 19 cm (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 6
    Subjects: Cleveland, Grover, 1837-1908 Inauguration, 1893.; Stevenson, Adlai E. (Adlai Ewing), 1835-1914. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n88159812; Cleveland, Grover, 1837-1908 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00009698; Stevenson, Adlai E. (Adlai Ewing), 1835-1914 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00243742; 1893 fast; Presidents United States Inauguration. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106479; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075771; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155
  - Inauguration reception, Grant, Colfax, March 4, 1869., Circa [1869]; Series 2; 1 card: illustrations; 19 x 25 cm (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 7
    Cataloger notes: Invitation to the inaugural reception.
    Subjects: Colfax, Schuyler, 1823-1885. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n85335914; Grant, Ulysses S. (Ulysses Simpson), 1822-1885 Inauguration, 1869. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n80126151; Colfax, Schuyler, 1823-1885 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00169199; Grant, Ulysses S. (Ulysses Simpson), 1822-1885 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00061535; 1869 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/33822; Presidents United States Inauguration. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106479; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01198743; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01075771; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01204155
  - Inaugural ceremonies; Washington, D.C., March 4th, 1897. Souvenir of National Capitol., Circa [1897?]; Series 2; 48 pages (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 8
    Subjects: McKinley, William, 1843-1901 Inauguration, 1897.; McKinley, William, 1843-1901. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00056763; 1897 fast; Presidents United States Inauguration. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106479; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075771; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155
  - Official programme of the inaugural ceremonies of Hon. William McKinley, of Ohio, and Hon. Garret A. Hobart, of New Jersey, as president and vice-president of the United States, at Washington, D.C., March 4, 1897; edition and compiler by Robert Schenck Fletcher and Fred W. Evans., Circa [1897]; Series 2; 96 pages illustrations 24 cm (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 9
    Subjects: McKinley, William, 1843-1901 Inauguration, 1897.; McKinley, William, 1843-1901. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00056763; 1897 fast; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743
  - Program for the inauguration of the President and Vice-President of the United States, March fourth, 1897., Circa [1897]; Series 2; 8 unnumbered pages; 18 x 26 cm (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 10
    Cataloger notes: Cover title: Inauguration, March 4th, 1897.
    Subjects: McKinley, William, 1843-1901 Inauguration, 1897. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n80079701; Presidents United States Inauguration, 1897.; Programs. rbgenr
  - Programs of the Inaugural Grand Concerts: Pension Building, Washington, D.C., March 5 and 6, 1897, given under the auspices of the Inaugural Executive Committee., Circa [1897]; Series 2; 7 pages; 17 cm (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 11
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Programs of concerts given at the inauguration of President McKinley and Vice President Roosevelt.; Source: Exchange with Stanford University, Oct. 14, 1958. DLC
    Subjects: McKinley, William, 1843-1901 Inauguration, 1897.; McKinley, William, 1843-1901 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00056763; 1897 fast; Concert programs Washington (D.C.); Concert programs. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00872991; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - Inaugural ceremonies, March 4, 1897: committees in charge and rules for their government, adopted by the executive committee, December 12, 1896., Circa [1896?]; Series 2; 42 pages; 13 x 17 cm (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 12
    Cataloger notes: In green illustrated paper covers.
    Subjects: McKinley, William, 1843-1901 Inauguration, 1897.; McKinley, William, 1843-1901 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00056763; 1897 fast; Presidents United States Inauguration. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106479; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075771; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155
  - Inaugural ball, March 4th, 1897., Circa [1897]; Series 2; 3 unnumbered leaves: illustrations, portraits; 18 x 25 cm (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 13
    Subjects: McKinley, William, 1843-1901 Inauguration, 1897.; McKinley, William, 1843-1901 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00056763; Pension Building (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh91002858; Pension Building (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00669375; 1897 fast; Presidents United States Inauguration. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106479; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075771; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155
  - Transportation rates to the inaugural ceremonies at Washington, March 4, 1897 by compiled and prepared from returns received; Charles J. Bell, Chairman Executive Committee in charge of Inaugural Ceremonies; Chapin Brown, Chairman Transportation Committee., Circa [1897]; Series 2; 32 pages; 14 cm (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 14
  - Final report of the chairman of the Executive Committee, Inaugural ceremonies, March 4, 1897., Series 2; 24 pages; 23 cm (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 15
    Cataloger notes: Cover title: Final report of the chairman of the Executive Committee of the Inaugural ceremonies of March 4, 1897.
  - Inaugural parade of March 4, 1897., Circa [1897]; Series 2; 4 items; 22-24 cm. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 16
    Cataloger notes: Headquarters of the Grand Marshal ... general orders numbers 5 -- Headquarters of the Grand Marshal ... general orders numbers 2 -- Headquarters of the Chief Marshal of the First Grand Division ... General order numbers 1 -- Headquarters, First Grand Division ... general orders numbers 2.
    Subjects: McKinley, William, 1843-1901 Inauguration, 1897.; McKinley, William, 1843-1901. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00056763; 1897 fast; Parades Washington (D.C.); Presidents United States Inauguration. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106479; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Parades. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01052822; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075771; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - McKinley and Hobart inaugural ball, March 4, 1897., Circa [1897]; Series 2; 12 pages; 12 cm (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 17
  - Programmes: inaugural grand concerts: Pension Building, Washington, D.C., March 5 and 6, nineteen hundred and one, given under the auspices of the Inaugural Committee., Circa [1901]; Series 2; 7 pages; 17 cm (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 18
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; In green illustrated paper covers. Pension building interior pictured on cover.; Programs for the concerts given at the inauguration of President Theodore Roosevelt.
    Subjects: Roosevelt, Theodore, 1858-1919 Inauguration, 1901.; Roosevelt, Theodore, 1858-1919 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00032496; Pension Building (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh91002858; Pension Building (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00669375; 1901 fast; Concert programs Washington (D.C.); Presidents United States Inauguration. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106479; Concert programs. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00872991; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075771; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Programs. rbgenr
  - Official programme of exercises and illustrated inaugural history commemorating the inauguration of Theodore Roosevelt as president of the United States, Charles W. Fairbanks as vice-president of the United States; illustrated with more than one hundred and fifty engravings., 1905; Series 2; 108 pages illustrations 28 cm (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 19
    Cataloger notes: Advertising matter interspersed.
    Subjects: Roosevelt, Theodore, 1858-1919 Inauguration, 1905.; Fairbanks, Charles Warren, 1852-1918.
  - Inaugural souvenir 1905., Series 2; [24] pages, [2] leaves of plates: illustrations, portraits; 24 cm (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 20
    Subjects: Roosevelt, Theodore, 1858-1919 Inauguration, 1905.; Roosevelt, Theodore, 1858-1919 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00032496; 1905 fast; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743
  - The nation's capital: [Washington D.C.] by O. Yates del., Circa [1905]; Series 2; 1 map; 45 x 42 cm (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 22
    Cataloger notes: Includes list of presidential inaugurations, directory of "Inaugural Committee, March 4, 1905," street width directory, and U.S. coat of arms.; Shows radial distances, locations of "Committee on Public Comfort" and "Inaugural Committee," and block numbers.; Available also through the Library of Congress Web site as a raster image.
    Subjects: Washington (D.C.) Maps. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008117384; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Maps. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423704; United States District of Columbia Washington. naf
  - [Notices]., Circa 1905]; Series 2; 2 items; 22 cm. (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 23
    Cataloger notes: Notices to members of the Floor Committee for the inauguration of President Theodore Roosevelt.
    Subjects: Roosevelt, Theodore, 1858-1919 Inauguration, 1905.; Roosevelt, Theodore, 1858-1919. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00032496; 1905 fast; Presidents United States Inauguration. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106479; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075771; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155
  - Official program, inauguration ceremonies, March 4, 1909., Circa [1909]; Series 2; 32 pages: illustrations, portraits; 23 cm (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 24
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; In illustrated paper covers.
    Subjects: Taft, William H. (William Howard), 1857-1930 Inauguration, 1909.; Taft, William H. (William Howard), 1857-1930 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00031956; 1909 fast; Presidents United States Inauguration. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106479; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075771; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155
  - Inauguration of William Howard Taft as President of the United States and James Schoolcraft Sherman as Vice-President of the United States: March 4, 1909: membership and duties of committees., Circa [1909]; Series 2; 59 pages; 24 cm (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 25
    Cataloger notes: In gray paper covers printed in black; ink signature of H.L. Hodgkins, member of the Reception Committee, on cover.
    Subjects: Sherman, J. S. (James Schoolcraft), 1855-1912. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n82009360; Taft, William H. (William Howard), 1857-1930 Inauguration, 1909.; Sherman, J. S. (James Schoolcraft), 1855-1912 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00249845; Taft, William H. (William Howard), 1857-1930 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00031956; 1909 fast; Presidents United States Inauguration. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106479; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075771; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155
  - Inaugural committee, 1912-13: Woodrow Wilson, New Jersey, President: Thomas R. Marshall, Indiana, Vice-President., Circa [1912]; Series 2; 1 folded sheet (4 pages); 22 cm (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 26
    Subjects: Wilson, Woodrow, 1856-1924 Inauguration, 1913.; Wilson, Woodrow, 1856-1924 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00034612; 1913 fast; Presidents United States Inauguration. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106479; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075771; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155
  - Official program, inauguration ceremonies, March fourth, 1913., Circa [1913]; Series 2; 32 unnumbered pages; 23 cm (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 27
    Subjects: Wilson, Woodrow, 1856-1924 Inauguration, 1913.; Wilson, Woodrow, 1856-1924 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00034612; 1913 fast; Presidents United States Inauguration. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106479; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075771; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155; Programs. rbgenr
  - Program of the ceremonies attending the inauguration of the President and Vice President of the United States at the National Capitol, March fifth, nineteen hundred and seventeen., Circa [1917]; Series 2; 10 unnumbered leaves; 23 cm (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 28
    Cataloger notes: Cover title: Inauguration ceremonies.
    Subjects: Wilson, Woodrow, 1856-1924 Inauguration, 1917.; Wilson, Woodrow, 1856-1924 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00034612; 1917 fast; Presidents United States Inauguration. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106479; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075771; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155
  - The official souvenir program, second inauguration, Woodrow Wilson, President, Thomas R. Marshall, Vice President of the United States, the fifth of March nineteen-seventeen., Circa [1917]; Series 2; [32] pages: illustrations; 28 cm (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 29
    Subjects: Wilson, Woodrow, 1856-1924 Inauguration, 1917.; Wilson, Woodrow, 1856-1924 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00034612; 1917 fast; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743
  - [Letter from the Committee]., Circa [1905]; Series 2; 1 sheet: illustrations; 28 cm (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 30
    Cataloger notes: Printed letter describing appropriate decorations on Pennsylvania Avenue for the inauguration of Theodore Roosevelt.
    Subjects: Roosevelt, Theodore, 1858-1919 Inauguration, 1905.; Roosevelt, Theodore, 1858-1919 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00032496; 1905 fast; Presidents United States Inauguration. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106479; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075771; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155
  - Points of historic interest in the national capital: selected by the Committee on Marking Points of Historic Interest., Circa [1929]; Series 2; iv, 59 pages: illustrations; 16 cm. (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 31
    Cataloger notes: "For the inauguration of Herbert Hoover as President of the United States, Washington, March 4, 1929."
  - Special AAA inaugural map of Washington, D.C.: showing main routes, temporary congested area, parking space on federal territory and information on public buildings issued by the District of Columbia Division of the American Automobile Association., Circa [1929?]; Series 2; 1 map; 20 x 27 cm (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 32
    Cataloger notes: Panel title.
    Subjects: Hoover, Herbert, 1874-1964 Inauguration, 1929.; Hoover, Herbert, 1874-1964. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00031698; 1929 fast; Presidents United States Inauguration. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106479; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075771; Washington (D.C.) Maps. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008117384; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Maps. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423704
  - Official program of the inaugural ceremonies inducting into office Franklin D. Roosevelt, President of the United States, John N. Garner, Vice President of the United States, March 4, 1933., Circa [1933]; Series 2; 64 pages: illustrations, portraits; 28 cm (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 33
    Subjects: Garner, John Nance, 1868-1967 Inauguration, 1933.; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945 Inauguration, 1933.; Garner, John Nance, 1868-1967. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00290696; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00032031; 1933 fast; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743
  - The honor of your presence is requested at the ceremonies attending the inauguration of the President of the United States, March fourth, nineteen hundred thirty-three., Circa [1933]; Series 2; 1 folded sheet (4 pages); 25 cm (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 34
    Cataloger notes: Includes a portrait of Roosevelt and one of John Nance Garner, and an envelope.; Invitation to inauguration of President Franklin D. Roosevelt.
    Subjects: Garner, John Nance, 1868-1967. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n91085097; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945 Inauguration, 1933.; Garner, John Nance, 1868-1967 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00290696; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00032031; 1933 fast; Presidents United States Inauguration. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106479; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075771; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155
  - Official program commemorating the inauguration of Harry S. Truman, President of the United States of America and Alben W. Barkley, Vice President of the United States of America., 1949; Series 2; 72 pages illustrations, portraits 29 cm (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 35
    Subjects: Barkley, Alben William, 1877-1956. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79056767; Truman, Harry S., 1884-1972 Inauguration.; Barkley, Alben William, 1877-1956. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00035952; Truman, Harry S., 1884-1972. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00032671; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743
  - Inaugural addresses of Dwight David Eisenhower, President of the United States: delivered at the Capitol, Washington, D.C. January 20, 1953 [and] January 21, 1957 by Dwight D. Eisenhower., Circa [1953-1957]; Series 2; 2 volumes in 1 (5, 4 pages); 22 cm. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 36
    Subjects: Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Dwight David), 1890-1969. Inaugural addresses. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79066408; Presidents United States Inaugural addresses. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106478
  - Complimentary guide book., Circa [1953]; Series 2; 64 pages illustrations, maps (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 37
    Subjects: Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Dwight David), 1890-1969 Inauguration. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79066408; Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Dwight David), 1890-1969. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00037714; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01198743
  - Inauguration, 1901: Metropolitan Police Department of the District of Columbia., Circa [1901]; Series 2; 8 pages; 20 cm (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 38
    Cataloger notes: "General orders, no. 103."; Caption title.; Signed: Richard Sylvester.
    Subjects: Police Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2010106860; Presidents United States Inauguration. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106479; Police. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01068398; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01075771; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01204155; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01204505
  - Inaugural ball, March 4, 1905: order of opening exercises., Circa [1905]; Series 2; 16 unnumbered pages; 12 cm (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 40
    Cataloger notes: Cover title: Inaugural ball March fourth 1905.; Included are three ribbons: street decorations committee, ball room decorations committee, inauguration usher.
    Subjects: Roosevelt, Theodore, 1858-1919 Inauguration, 1905.; Roosevelt, Theodore, 1858-1919 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00032496; 1905 fast; Presidents United States Inauguration. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106479; Ribbons. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85113847; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075771; Ribbons. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01097313; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155; Programs. rbgenr
  - Points of historic interest: inauguration of Wilson and Marshall, Washington, March 4, 1913 selected by the Committee on Marking Points of Historic Interest., Circa [1913]; Series 2; 48 pages: illustrations, map; 16 cm (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 41